<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stanley Semilla</title>
    <description>The awesome life of Stanley</description>
    <link>http://semillastan.github.iohttp://semillastan.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://semillastan.github.iohttp://semillastan.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>After work</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Let me tell you a story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what I usually do. For the previous months, my work schedule starts at 10 in the morning and ends at 7 in the evening. For 5 days in a week, that is the schedule that I have to follow. Since I am a freelancer also, I do have side projects that needs to be completed within the timeline given by the clients. Everyday, I spend more than 8 hours of coding, both back-end and front-end. The best part of my life is still having time for myself, my family and my partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Programming is always fun for me. I enjoy it too much that everyday I think of something new to learn and develop. My goal is to be able to learn several ways of building things. This goal gives me a boost among others. I learned not to be dependent on one thing. Be better at something, and get yourself learning a new one. But of course, we do feel tired most of the time. Once I stop coding, I will always end up watching a series or playing a game. Until now, I love to play Counter Strike even if I’m not very good at it. I know that I won’t be a professional with CS:GO, but I do watch tournaments and get to know the strategies they are doing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://semillastan.github.iohttp://semillastan.github.io/2015/07/22/after-work/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://semillastan.github.iohttp://semillastan.github.io/2015/07/22/after-work/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The life of Stanley</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The awesome life of Stanley begins here (again).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an attempt to create the best way of showing who Stanley is, this page was created. Finally, a decision was made: to stay with Github Pages together with Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://semillastan.github.iohttp://semillastan.github.io/2015/07/20/blogging-with-jekyll/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://semillastan.github.iohttp://semillastan.github.io/2015/07/20/blogging-with-jekyll/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
